You've finally come out, Dio.
A job well done, Polnareff.
You managed to avenge your sister.
But what's most impressive is that you
also found the time to track me down. Ha!
I'll gladly kill you to celebrate.
But I think we should
start with this first.
I'll give you a chance to rethink.
Descend now and not only will you live,
you'll be given the
chance to serve me again.
Or you could choose to rise forth.
However, you'd be ascending to your doom.
When the two of us first met,
fear consumed me like a curse.
It gave your evil Card blanche
to manipulate me like a puppet.
That fear was the beginning of a
futile existence with no end in sight.
It was a fate worse than death.
A wretched life devoid of any desire
other than doing your bidding.
But that fear has been eradicated,
leaving only the burning will to fight.
I've spent 45 days traveling with Mr.
Joestar and the others
and in honor of those who
died on that journey I'll
never fear you again.
My aren't we confident climb these
stairs and put that bravado to the test?
Quite the interesting decision Polnareff.
You've backed down after
all is that your clever
way of telling me you
want your former life?
back.
What in the hell?
But I went up the stairs. I'm
sure. What happened? Problem?
You seem to be shaken, Polnareff.
But why is that?
Could the winds of fear have
extinguished your burning resolve?
Perhaps the only steps you
took were in your mind.
And in actuality, fear overrode
your Your consciousness,
wrestling control from your brain
causing you to descend down the stairs.
No way!
I'm positive I just
walked up those stairs!
What?
Is he doing this with his stand?
No!
It couldn't be!
Dio's stand is...
...the world?!
What am I supposed to do now?
Once I come back to the jump and
see it, I will never let it be.
We will still look at the
place where we'll see.
We will still see the chance of the
battle, the time we will not look at it.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry. Let's go.
And the story of the story started.
I'll be able to take a moment.
I'll be able to continue.
The Crusaders.
The last page of the stars.
I'll be able to take that.
End of the world!
I'll be able to take that!
I'll be able to take that.
I'm curious, Polnareff.
Have you ever wondered what
the human soul desires most?
Peace of mind.
Subconsciously, all humans
wish to overcome their fears.
They seek fame,
money, and dominance of others, all to
obtain a sense of everlasting security.
What a farce.
They create bonds as a
means of self-preservation.
They say they wish to help others,
purely for the sake of love and justice.
But it's only to settle
their feeble minds.
Humanity's greatest desire
is to latch on to serenity.
So why?
Why refuse to serve me?
What greater serenity is there?
Return to me, and all I
speak of will be yours.
You don't want to challenge me.
There's just no point in running
headlong into a meaningless death.
You deserve much more.
No!
Am I seriously letting
him draw me back in?
You're a talented stand user.
It would be a shame to kill you.
Turn your back on Joestar
and live as my right hand.
I promise you unending peace starting now.
I have to resist.
Avdol, Iggy, I need your courage.
Cut the bullshit, Dio!
I've already stared death in the eye!
And I'll gladly do it again, if it
helps uncover your stand's abilities!
How disappointing.
Time to meet your end, Polnareff!
So that's your stand, the world! Bring it!
It's... Mr. Joestar!
There's no need to worry, Paul the Rep.
Dio!
That was Dio!
After him!
I have to tell you something first!
It was only out in the open for a moment
or two, but I saw him use his stand.
Well, I didn't actually see it, but I
did feel it in a manner of speaking.
It's complicated, but here's
the long and short of it.
I was heading up the stairs
to beat the life out of
that bastard when suddenly
I was back where I started.
Believe me, I know what I'm saying
doesn't make any sense at all.
I can't wrap my head around
what happened either.
I feel like I'm losing my mind over here.
I'm sure he wasn't using
any sort of hypnosis.
I'd say super speed, but there's no way.
All I know is that I sense
something utterly terrifying.
Hey, where are Iggy and Avdol?
They didn't make it. They're both dead.
They died trying to save me.
Is that so?
We should go.
Look, Mr.
Joestar, the sun is setting.
Let's hurry.
Yeah, you're right.
All right, out with it.
What's waiting for us upstairs?
The...
the towers!
There's also another room at the top!
It's where Lord Dio dwells during the day!
Is there another staircase to the tower?
No, this is the only set
of stairs that leads there!
In that case, lead the way.
So that's him.
The two of us have never met.
But I've known about this monster
for longer than I care to remember.
How could I not know this fiend?
The thought of him has been burned into
my mind ever since the day I was born.
Same for Jotaro.
We'd hoped this day would never come,
that we'd never have to face Dio.
But as Joestars, we knew we'd
eventually have to destroy him.
I have no regrets.
I came on this journey
of my own free will,
so I can live with whatever
happens from here on out.
I've never seen things more clearly.
It's like a light of
clarity has washed over me.
My friends are that light,
while Dio is darkness.
My body may be broken and battered,
but the fear has vanished.
Virtue and light has purified my soul.
We'll attack the moment Dio
steps out of the coffin.
Stay at the ready.
We don't know what tricks
he has up his sleeves.
It's time, loser.
Open the coffin.
Whatever happens, ordeal, you
have to know I never betrayed you.
I only led these
degenerates here because I
knew you had the power to
easily dispose of them!
As certain as a man wetting
himself when pissing in the wind,
your victory is assured
you are all-powerful!
Please don't be angry with me!
Enough of the groveling!
Open the damn coffin!
Please, I'm begging you!
Give these bastards a
cruel and horrifying end!
Ordeal!
Get ready, everyone.
I don't know what's going
on how'd I get in here I was
just what the hell how did he
my eyes were locked on loser
boy the entire time did
anyone else see him get in the
coffin wait did someone put him
in there without us knowing no
I was watching him just like
you were he's opening the
coffin one second and the next
he's inside it you're right
polnareff but I don't believe
it's a mind trick and it's
not super speed either good
grief is he playing games with us
get out of here damn you
what are you doing come on?
Let me go!
Okay, what was that feeling back there?
The ominous presence it was
giving off was far more powerful
than any stand our group
has ever encountered before!
It was like knowing a
bulldozer is coming after
you just from the sound
of its roaring engine!
Yeah, I sensed it too!
An insane lust to kill us!
It felt like somebody
shoving an icicle up my ass!
If we hadn't escaped when we did, whatever
that was would have killed us for sure!
Damn it!
Just look at the sun!
It's almost gone below the horizon!
Dio will have the advantage in the dark.
Hang on!
Come again?
Please don't tell me you guys are
planning to run away and hide until dawn.
Listen to me, Mr. Joestar.
I'm finishing this.
There's no way I'm packing
up and heading for the hills.
You're right.
We have to see this through to the end.
I want to get this over
with as much as you do.
But the tide of battle has turned.
While not up close, we
face to stand the world.
But we still have no
idea what its powers are.
We're fighting blind here.
Think of it this way.
It's like mountain climbing
without knowing the route.
If we try to fight Dio
right now, we'll all die.
That fact is as inevitable as burping
after knocking back a couple of colas.
Dio would be a fool not
to come racing after us,
but he only has until Sunrise to kill us.
In the meantime,
we need to learn the extent of his stance
power and find a way to put him down.
If we can just hold out
until then... No way!
I'm not going back on my word.
Avdol and Iggy died
because of my weakness.
I have to kill Dio.
I'll go to hell and back to do it,
but all I won't do is run
away from my obligation! No!
Come back, Polnareff! Forget it.
He's not gonna listen.
Jotaro, what do you
think we should do now?
He went down there to fight Dio.
As we retreat, we'll also be fighting him.
Which means we'll be attacking
from both sides at once.
Hey, buddy, let us buy this truck off you.
What do you say?
The hell is wrong with you?
This baby's my bread and butter.
No, wait, it's all yours.
Buckle up, cock-o-een.
There you are, Dio.
Think I'll just run till dawn?
You've crossed the wrong Frenchman.
I'll settle this on my own if I have to.
So what if I don't know
how Dio's stand works?
I'll just find another way to defeat him.
He's dead.
Hold it, Polnareff.
I had them let you go because convincing
stubborn guys like you
is a pain in the ass.
But the old men in Kakyoin insisted
I stay close and watch your back.
So here I am. Totoro!
Oh, good grief.
The automobile.
Such impressive power and speed.
When I was young, all we had were
shabby horse-drawn carriages.
Don't move!
What do you think you're doing?
This car belongs to U .S.
Senator Mr.
Phillips, and touching
it results in a beatdown!
What the hell's wrong with you?
My,
my, young people these days are so full
of piss and vinegar Times are a-changin'.
Why would you?
Stop talking now and
proceed to the front seat.
It's time to drive.
Just who the hell are you, Seiko?
After I'm finished with you, you'll rue
the day you ever march into my vehicle.
Yeah, this is unforgivable.
No one gets away with doing
something like this to me.
I was valedictorian in both
high school and college,
not to mention captain of
the college wrestling team.
Even after graduation,
people respected me.
That's how I became a politician!
I own a villa on a thousand-acre
plot of land in Hawaii.
My gorgeous model of a
wife is 25 years younger,
and I pay more taxes than anyone else!
I've destroyed every enemy
who's ever stood in my way,
and someday I'll become president!
I'm THE Senator Phillips, damn it!
Listen to me, you punk band reject!
I'm gonna make sure you rot in
prison for the rest of your misery!
Hear this, as I won't repeat it.
Drive the car.
This psychopath's gonna kill me.
I have to get the hell out of this car.
If I don't, I'm a goner.
Someone help me.
What the hell?
Huh?
What's that?
I'm positive I jumped out of the car.
So what the hell am I
doing back in the car?
I don't get it!
What's going on?
Your job is to catch up to that truck.
Fail to do so and you die.
Yes, sir!
How am I still in the car?
Of course. That's it.
I'm a senator.
What can't I do?
Yes, it makes total sense now!
I still sense D .O.'s sinister bloodlust.
Its presence is overwhelming.
He's coming for us.
You can bet your ass he's on our trail.
Are you saying that D .O.
somehow knows our precise location?
Not quite.
He stole the body of my
grandfather, Jonathan Joestar.
I can sense his body, but I can't
tell if he's nearby or far away.
I have a general feeling, but I
don't know exactly where he is.
It's like when we got to Cairo,
and while I knew he was here,
I couldn't pinpoint his lair.
Lucky for us, the same thing goes for Dio.
All he knows is that we're nearby,
but he's unable to tell
the difference between us.
And he probably doesn't know we've
separated, which is good for now.
Why the hell isn't this working?
Cars always start up when they
do this kind of thing in movies.
seems like there's a traffic jam
I'm sorry sir the evening commute is
always bumper-to-bumper move it but
we're stuck here there's just too
much traffic have you forgotten there's
a sidewalk use it the sidewalk but
it's covered with people heading home
from work and your point go yes sir
faster yes sir
okay it's running hurry up
and get on Polnareff oh yeah
oh the things I do for you but I've
done everything you've asked so
you'll spare my life right there's
no need to kill a helpless senator
Wrong.
I have to be dreaming.
What other explanation is there?
As if a senator like me could be killed.
It's just a dream!
Found you.
Now get closer.
We need to catch up to them.
I can't use the world
if I'm this far away.
Look, here he comes.
You see that car?
That's Dio's ride.
Hakuin!
It's Kakyoinz.
Take this, Dio!
Emerald Splash!
Unbelievable!
He deflected my attack
with the flick of a finger!
He barely moved!
But how do you like this?
He even dodged the
concentrated splash? Damn it!
When did he bring out his stand?
How could I have missed that?
Well, that's a shame.
He's too far away now.
My punch seems to have thrown
him out of the world's range.
Ah!
What's happening?
And what precisely would I gain by
explaining this situation to you?
Pay attention to the road and drive.
Be careful, Kakyoin.
You were way too close to it.
Please, forgive me.
I didn't mean...
It was only a few months
ago when Dio asked
me if I was really going
to vomit out of fear.
That monster had the audacity
to tell me I should relax.
Bastard!
Never again!
I'll never lose to you again!
Are you alright, Kakyoin?
Did you catch a glimpse of the world?
Yes, I saw it when I attacked
Dio from ten meters away.
If I had gotten any closer,
I would have been done for.
But we know one thing for certain.
His stand holds a power more horrific
than we could have ever imagined.
However, we know two things about it.
First,
his stand doesn't have the reach of my
Hierophant Green or your Hermit Purple.
It's a close-range power stand,
like Star Platinum, and has
a range of about 10 meters.
Second,
it attacked with its fist, so it doesn't
use projectile weapons like bullets.
That being said,
if we can sneak up on
him and get within range,
we just might have a chance
of finishing him off.
We have to figure out his secret.
Even so, we have to exercise extreme
caution when approaching this bastard.
Hold on.
Why does car suddenly stop?
Incoming!
We're about to be hit!
Mr. Joestar!
What are you doing, Kakyoin?
I understand now.
I know now how to uncover
the secret of Dio's stand.
Thank you.
Whenever I think about Avdol and Iggy,
it makes the hairs on the
back of my neck stand on end.
I'm sure it's because they were the
first to treat me like a friend.
My friends and I were on
a journey to defeat Dio.
All right, here it comes!